Lesson four, Nicole's day at school.
Nicole tells her mother Susan about her successful presentation at school.
Her brother Ted overhears and interrupts the conversation.
How was your day at school today, Nicole?
It was great, mom.
I gave a presentation on Hillary Clinton in government class.
Afterwards, my teacher paid me a compliment.
What did she say?
She said my presentation was head and shoulders above the others.
Way to go.
She also said I should go into politics just like Hillary.
You're so gung-ho about school. It drives me crazy.
Ted, don't butt in. You're just jealous.
Right, you hit the nail on the head. I'm green with envy.
Would you just shut up? You're on thin ice with me right now.
Oh no, look at me. I'm shaking in my shoes.
You're on thin ice with me right now.